<?xml version = "1.0" ?>
<research>
	
<!-- ======================================== Wand of the Tinkerer /-->
<project id = "WAND_TINKERER" version = "1">
<name>Wand of the Tinkerer</name>
<popupText>[TT] Store more in less</popupText>
<longText>You decided that the Wand of the Adept won't be enough for the magic you are trying to do. You have formulated a theory for a more advanced wand that can hold a fair bit more vis.</longText>
<page type = "text">After learning more about the Aura through direct inspection of it using the Goggles of Revealing, you decided you need a better wand, thus, you formulated a wand perfect for an experienced Tinkerer.

This wand can carry 500 vis, unlike the Wand of the Adept. It's not a very dispendious item either. The downside of being forced to store more vis, is that it recharges slower in comparison to it's counterpart, the Wand of the Adept.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">WAND_TINKERER</page>
</project>
	
<!-- ======================================== Gaseous Glowstone /-->
<project id = "GLOWSTONE_GAS" version = "2">
<name>Gaseous Glowstone</name>
<popupText>[TT] Shiny Air</popupText>
<longText>Researching the intricacies of the Light is paying off, you are close to finding a way to make completely invisible light.</longText>
<page type = "text">You have studied the intricacies of the Light, and found out a way to create completely invisible light by infusing Glowstone with the raw flame. 

This phial contains a concentrated extract of Gaseous Glowstone, that can be released through a right click, and will spread relatively fast in the nearby area, lighting it up.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">GLOWSTONE_GAS</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Spellbinding Cloth /-->
<project id = "SPELL_CLOTH" version = "1">
<name>Spellbinding Cloth</name>
<popupText>[TT] Wipe off the bad luck</popupText>
<longText>You've had enough with gambling on the Enchantment Table, and you seem to be figuring out a cloth that will allow you to remove those poor and unwanted enchantments.</longText>
<page type = "text">By mixing some Enchanted Fabric with raw Enchantment power, you created a cloth that can be rubbed on an item to wipe it of it's enchantments by combining them in a Crafting Recipe.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">SPELL_CLOTH</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Stopwatch of the Timebender /-->
<project id = "STOPWATCH" version = "1">
<name>Stopwatch of the Timetwister</name>
<popupText>[TT] 1.21 GIGAWATTS!?!</popupText>
<longText>You think you know a way of twisting the very fabric of time to your will.</longText>
<page type = "text">You have found a way of twisting the very fabric of time to your own will. 

With a simple click of this stopwatch you can bind your position, health, and food to it. One minute later, if you still have the watch in your possession, you will be returned to this point.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">STOPWATCH</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Wand of Dislocation /-->
<project id = "WAND_DISLOCATION" version = "1">
<name>Wand of Dislocation</name>
<popupText>[TT] Now you see it, now you don't</popupText>
<longText>After studying the Wand of Equal Trade, you figured you can use it's powers to store, and move things around more effectively.</longText>
<page type = "text">After studying the Wand of Equal Trade, you found a way to use it in order to store, and move things around. 

Right clicking on one block will encase it into the wand. Right clicking with a block in the wand will move it elsewhere.

This power is provenient from the portable hole, so your new wand will be able to get anything the portable hole can.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">WAND_DISLOCATION</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Golem Name Tag /-->
<project id = "NAMETAG" version = "1">
<name>Golem Name Tag</name>
<popupText>[TT] Hello! My name is...</popupText>
<longText>Some black dye and magic... and you think you have figured out a way to properly name your golems.</longText>
<page type = "text">A name tag with some magic. Giving it to one of your golem minions will have them show off their name.

To do this, the item must be named in an anvil, one would left click the golem with the named item. This does not hit, or damage the golem.</page>
<page type = "arcanecrafting">NAMETAG</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Transmutator /-->
<project id = "TRANSMUTATOR" version = "1">
<name>Arcane Transmutator</name>
<popupText>[TT] Inequivalent Exchange</popupText>
<longText>Researching The Aura is becoming important. You seem to have figured out a way to directly conjure vis from the aura into matter.</longText>
<page type = "text">After researching further into the intricacies of the Aura itself, you have found out a way to directly siphon it's vis, and using aspects from nearby aspectual sources, conjure it into matter.

This block can accept an item to be used as a pattern to create a new one. Only simple items, in terms of aspect count can be created, and in doing so, it takes both vis from the aura, and the quadruple of each aspect from that item.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">TRANSMUTATOR</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Talisman of Withhold /-->
<project id = "XP_TALISMAN" version = "1">
<name>Talisman of Withhold</name>
<popupText>[TT] Talisman o' Enchanting</popupText>
<longText>Knowing that Zombie Brains, when used well, have the ability to store experience, you are trying to figure out a way to make them portable.</longText>
<page type = "text">After knowing that Zombie Brains have the ability to store experience, you have created a talisman that mimics that behaviour, not to a perfect extent though.

To switch the ability to store experience, you need to shift-right-click on the talisman. When the talisman is enabled, it'll absorb any nearby experience orbs, those can be transformed back into useable experience by right clicking with a glass bottle in your inventory, turning that bottle into a Bottle o' Enchanting.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">XP_TALISMAN</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Infernal Bracelet /-->
<project id = "FIRE_BRACELET" version = "1">
<name>Infernal Bracelet</name>
<popupText>[TT] Hands of Hell</popupText>
<longText>Knowing the power of an Infernal Furnace, you are trying to figure out how to bring that power with you for better usage.</longText>
<page type = "text">Knowing the ability of an Infernal Furnace to smelt items, you went on to study a way of using that power from your hands.

This bracelet smelts blocks in the world with a right click on them. In order for it to do so, it needs to be charged by right clicking on an active Arcane Bellows, in order to convey the energy of the furnace.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">FIRE_BRACELET</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Warded Chest /-->
<project id = "WARD_CHEST" version = "1">
<name>Warded Chest</name>
<popupText>[TT] Safe as can be</popupText>
<longText>Knowing how safe Warded blocks can be, you are trying to find out a way to make them into item storage.</longText>
<page type = "text">After creating, and working with Warded Blocks, you have discovered a way of making them into storage. This chest is completely safe and can only be opened by the person who placed it. It also has an extended storage space.

Similarly to Warded Blocks, this chest can be removed with a wand. On a negative note, the chest lacks a keyhole.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">WARD_CHEST</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Smokey Quartz /-->
<project id = "DARK_QUARTZ" version = "1">
<name>Smokey Quartz</name>
<popupText>[TT] Inverted Looks</popupText>
<page type = "text">Smokey Quartz is pretty much Quartz, but negative. All regular blocks that can be made with quartz, can also be made with smokey quartz, and they look black.

Smokey Quartz itself can be made with a piece of coal or charcoal for tinting, and a few pieces of regular nether quartz.</page>
<page type = "crafting">DARK_QUARTZ0</page>
<page type = "crafting">DARK_QUARTZ1</page>
<page type = "crafting">DARK_QUARTZ2</page>
<page type = "crafting">DARK_QUARTZ3</page>
<page type = "crafting">DARK_QUARTZ4</page>
<page type = "crafting">DARK_QUARTZ5</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Sigil of Memories /-->
<project id = "TELEPORTATION_SIGIL" version = "1">
<name>Sigil of Memories</name>
<popupText>[TT] I recall this...</popupText>
<longText>You are planning on creating an item that will allow you return to where you once were before. Some eldritch magic should do...</longText>
<page type = "text">You have created an item that allows you to return to where you've been before. By right clicking with this sigil somewhere, it'll be bound to it.

After a sigil is bound, you can hold right click it, like a bow to charge it and activate it, which teleports you back to where the sigil was bound at. Shattering it in the proceess.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">TELEPORTATION_SIGIL</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Wand of Uprising /-->
<project id = "WAND_UPRISING" version = "1">
<name>Wand of Uprising</name>
<popupText>[TT] I believe I can fly...</popupText>
<longText>Knowing the power of the Sword of the Zephyr to propel foes away, you are trying to create something that will allow you to propel yourself.</longText>
<page type = "text">Using the knowledge you got from creating the Sword of the Zephyr of propeling things around with air, you created a wand that will propel the holder in the direction that they're looking at.

While someone is flying through the use of this Wand, any fall damage that would have been taken is negated.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">WAND_UPRISING</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Sword of the Condor /-->
<project id = "SWORD_CONDOR" version = "1"> 
<name>Sword of the Condor</name>
<popupText>[TT] Woosh!</popupText>
<longText>Unsatisfacted with the effort you put on the Wand of Uprising, you are trying to combine it with the Sword of the Zephyr in hopes of getting better results.</longText>
<page type = "text">You have found a way of combining the Sword of the Zephyr with your latest creation, the Wand of Uprising. By doing so, you managed to duplicate the effect of the wand used, albeit at a faster speed. It's also possible to sneak right-click to be propeled backwards.

Doing such, however, comes with a few drawbacks. The sword loses it's ability to propel nearby foes, or slow your fall, not to mention that this flight is hard to control. However, by reinforcing the sword with extra Thaumium, it became extremely resistent.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">SWORD_CONDOR</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Rune Thanatos /-->
<project id = "DEATH_RUNE" version = "1"> 
<name>Rune Thanatos</name>
<popupText>[TT] The Extra H is for "Hamazing"!</popupText>
<longText>That last time you got blown up by a creeper right next to a lava lake was a big loss. To that, you are trying to research death itself to find ways of securing your belongings.</longText>
<page type = "text">By studying Death itself, you found a way of making use of the powers of item storage you learned from creating Warded Chests, and made a way to secure your belongings upon death.

When you die with this item on you. All that you are carrying gets stored in it. The rune will then stay where you died, it's invulnerable, and doesn't despawn. When you come back to it, your inventory will get reorganized to it's original state before death, as best as possible. The rune will shatter in the process.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">DEATH_RUNE</page>
</project>


<!-- ======================================== Tool Dynamism /-->
<project id = "ANIMATION_TABLET" version = "1"> 
<name>Tool Dynamism</name>
<popupText>[TT] Stationary Animation</popupText>
<longText>After learning further into golemancy, you are confident that you can put the Golem Animation Core to create something else than golems...</longText>
<page type = "text">You decided to further discover the uses of Golem Animation Cores, and this is the fruit of that labour.

This tablet can accept an item to animate with mystical energy. Using the left and right buttons in the tablet's interface, you can select to do a left or right click with the item. The button in the bottom controls if the tablet reacts always when it can or just when a redstone signal is applied.

Virtually anything can be animated, including blocks. The type of tool in the tablet also defines how fast something breaks, as expected.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">ANIMATION_TABLET</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Silk Cutter /-->
<project id = "SILK_SWORD" version = "1"> 
<name>Silk Cutter</name>
<popupText>[TT] Sharp n' Smooth</popupText>
<longText>The knowledge you found speaks of a powerful tool that bears the Silk Touch enchantment. You are wondering how to create it, but are sure some cloth will be required.</longText>
<page type = "text">The texts you studied spoke of a powerful tool that beared the Silk Touch enchantment. You seem to have managed to replicate it.

This item acts as an "omnitool" of sorts, it can break virtually anything, but it's not very fast at it. You think enchanting it with Efficiency using an anvil is the logical next step.

Furthermore, after crafting this item, it instantly comes enchanted with the Silk Touch enchantment. The one downside to this is that it can't be enchanted through regular means. It also seems to hold it's magical energy with a extraordinary bond, possibly unbreakable.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">SILK_SWORD</page>
</project>

<!-- ======================================== Fortunate Maul /-->
<project id = "FORTUNE_MAUL" version = "1"> 
<name>Fortunate Maul</name>
<popupText>[TT] Rarity Hunter</popupText>
<longText>The knowledge you found speaks of a powerful tool that bears the Fortune enchantment. You are wondering how to create it, but are sure some valuable goods will be required.</longText>
<page type = "text">The texts you studied spoke of a powerful tool that beared the Fortune enchantment. You seem to have managed to replicate it.

This item acts as an "omnitool" of sorts, it can break virtually anything, but it's not very fast at it. You think enchanting it with Efficiency using an anvil is the logical next step.

Furthermore, after crafting this item, it instantly comes enchanted with the Fortune III enchantment. The one downside to this is that it can't be enchanted through regular means. It also seems to hold it's magical energy with a extraordinary bond, possibly unbreakable.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">FORTUNE_MAUL</page>
</project>


<!-- ======================================== Ender Mirror /-->
<project id = "FNDER_MIRROR" version = "1"> 
<name>Ender Mirror</name>
<popupText>[TT] Another sight</popupText>
<longText>After learning how to transport items using Hand Mirrors, you are thinking you can apply that knowledge to the Ender Chests.</longText>
<page type = "text">You have put the knowledge acquired from constructing the Magic Hand Mirror into good use, and applied it to the Ender Chests.

This mirror, for a small cost of vis from the local aura allows you to access your ender chest inventory without needing to place it down yourself.</page>
<page type = "infusioncrafting">ENDER_MIRROR</page>
</project>
</research>